Krunal Parmar

9879483495 krunal85parmar@gmail.com Shilaj, Ahmedabad

Profile

A Human Resources Manager with 15+ years of experience specializing in HR administration, employee relations, process improvement, and payroll administration. A strong background in overseeing HR business management functions and driving the implementation of HRIS technologies to enhance organizational effectiveness.

Professional Experience

Human Resources Manager, Legalwiz.in Private Limited

October 2020 - Present

- Oversee all HR functions for 80+staff, lead the response to labor and compensation issues, conduct recruitment initiatives, manage employee onboarding activities as well as Payroll
- Develop an overarching strategy to improve employee relations and crossfunctional collaboration, including establishing the employee resource group and planning events to drive employee engagement
- Looking after for all Compliance issues like PF, ESIC, PT etc.
- Taking care for entire Admin Department as well
- Vendor Coordination, Payment of Vendor Etc.

Human Resource Manager, Entigrity Private Limited

January 2019 – March 2020

- Managed all HR processes for 200+ employees across three locations, oversaw recruiting, hiring, and onboarding activities, established standardized training processes, and created a database to facilitate knowledge sharing
- Served as the point of contact for HR matters, identified solutions to employee conflicts, benefits issues, and compensation, and created a new performance appraisal system
- Taking care for entire Admin activity of the company

Human Resource Manager, Pacific Global Solutions Pvt Ltd

September 2015 – December 2018

- Overseeing the day-to-day HR management of employee with a direct responsibility with across 150+ employees.
- Handle team of 6 Executives for entire Ahmedabad & Mumbai location.
- Providing overall leadership and guidance on talent acquisition, career development, succession planning, retention, training and leadership development, compensation and benefits.
- Assisting with recruitment, developing roles and identifying future needs.
- Taking care for entire Admin activity of the company

Team Leader, Team Lease Services Pvt. Ltd.

July 2014 - September 2015

- Taking care for entire recruitment process for Gujarat State.
- Handle team of 5 Executives for 4 Location.
- Client coordination, Feedback, Follow up for new vacancies
- Bulk Recruitment and Bulk Hiring for client on remote places.
- Taking care for Onboarding and Payrolling of candidates

Candidate Manager, Adecco India Pvt. Ltd.

August 2011 - June 2014

- Providing support to recruitment for smooth process.
- Providing support with data of candidates.
- Collaboration with all B School, ITI Institute and Local Collages
- Bulk Recruitment and Bulk Hiring for client on remote places.
- Campus Interview and Campus hiring on behalf of client and company

Sr. Consultant Contract Recruitment, Kelly Services India Pvt. Ltd.

November 2008 – August 2011

- Involved end to end recruitment for Contract and permanent Staffing.
- Bulk recruitment of client for Blue Collar and White Collar.
- Coordinating with client on recruitment process and feedback.
- Handling recruitment for across Gujarat State

Recruitment Executive, Karma Recruitments Pvt. Ltd.

November 2007 - November 2008

- Involved end to end recruitment for Contract and permanent Staffing.
- Bulk recruitment of client for Blue Collar and White Collar.
- Coordinating with client on recruitment process and feedback.
- Handling recruitment for across Gujarat State

Education

Post Graduate Diploma in Human Resource Management

National Education Management

Professional Programme in Human Resource Management

NR Institute of Business Management (NRIBM - GLS University)

Diploma in Electrical Engineering

Technical Education Board - Gujarat

Key Skills

- HR Management
- HRIS Technology
- Talent Recruitment
- Payroll Administration
- Process Improvement